<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connor Shade</title>
    <link>https://connorshade.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Connor Shade</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Connor Shade</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:20:46 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://connorshade.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Setup</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/post/hugo-setup/hugo-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 17:20:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/post/hugo-setup/hugo-setup/</guid>
      <description>My deployment is now (almost) entirely automated. I write Markdown files in one repo, push the changes, and my site in another repo is automatically rebuilt - changes appear to my website about a minute after my push.
Repo structure I have two GitHub repositories I&amp;rsquo;m using for this blog:
cnnrshd/connorshade.com - This repo holds the output of my hugo new site connorshade.com command. Everything hugo-related is here: Themes, content, images, the hugo config, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 10:17:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of all projects that are hosted on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Nmap Scan</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/writing-nmap-scan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:26:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/writing-nmap-scan/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the second part of &amp;ldquo;service-to-shell&amp;rdquo;. In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll outline the process of making a custom nmap match directive that can be used to detect services that may not have an existing nmap directive. This can be especially useful when dealing with custom applications. Here&amp;rsquo;s an overview of what I&amp;rsquo;ll cover:
Modifying the dnssearcher service to report a banner The basic layout of an nmap service probe file Writing a custom nmap service probe to detect dnssearcher and extract the version Strip the probe to run banner scans 100x faster than default Reporting a banner By default, uvicorn will use the Server header of &amp;ldquo;uvicorn&amp;rdquo; in the response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a Vulnerable Webapp</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/vulnerable-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:43:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/vulnerable-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Part One in my &amp;ldquo;service-to-shell&amp;rdquo; series. I want to make a vulnerable webapp that I can scan with a custom nmap probe and exploit with a custom Metasploit module.
This post covers making the vulnerable webapp - not as exciting as a custom Metasploit module or as useful as an additional nmap banner scanner, but an essential part of the project. For making a vulnerable webapp, the first step is to pick the language (I went with Python), then the vulnerability (Command injection - it&amp;rsquo;s simple to write and understand), and finally the theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Author</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/author/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/author/</guid>
      <description>I like to work at the intersection of Security and Automation. I enjoy building content and training. I have a wide range of experience, from Networking and System Administration to Offensive and Defensive security.
Seeking Opportunities I&amp;rsquo;m currently looking for new opportunities in Cyber Security (or adjacent fields). Check out my LinkedIn for more details on positions I&amp;rsquo;ve had, or reach out to me at the info below.
Contact me I can be contacted at blog for blog-related messages or jobs for job-related messages, @thisdomain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro Post</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/post/intro/intro-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/post/intro/intro-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome. This is my blog for the time being.
Content Expect content to be: projects I work on, stuff I do, focused on tech.
Hosting The address (connorshade.com) should never change, but the theme and hosting provider may. Right now I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;hosting&amp;rdquo; on Github pages - posts are built with Hugo and I&amp;rsquo;m using the bear cub theme because it seems simple enough.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
