<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connor Shade</title>
    <link>https://connorshade.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Connor Shade</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:20:46 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://connorshade.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 10:17:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of all projects that are hosted on this blog. Projects are a subset of sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a Vulnerable Webapp</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/vulnerable-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:43:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/vulnerable-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Part One in a three part series that I&amp;rsquo;ve called &amp;ldquo;service-to-shell&amp;rdquo;. I want to make a vulnerable webapp that I can scan with a custom nmap probe and exploit with a custom Metasploit module.
This post covers making the vulnerable webapp - not as exciting as a custom Metasploit module or as useful as an additional nmap banner scanner, but an essential part of the process. For making a vulnerable webapp, the first step is to pick the language (I went with Python), then the vulnerability (Command injection - it&amp;rsquo;s simple to write and understand), and finally the theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Author</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/author/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/author/</guid>
      <description>I like to work at the intersection of Security and Automation. I enjoy building content and training. The blog is a work in progress - trying to get the pipeline working well. Expect some oddities (missing images, notes in posts)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Sections</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/sections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/sections/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of all sections in this blog along with a short description. Sections includes projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro Post</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/post/intro/intro-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/post/intro/intro-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome. This is my blog for the time being.
Content Expect content to be: projects I work on, stuff I do, focused on tech.
Hosting The address (connorshade.com) should never change, but the theme and hosting provider may. Right now I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;hosting&amp;rdquo; on Github pages - posts are built with Hugo and I&amp;rsquo;m using the bear cub theme because it seems simple enough. I tried to use Gruvbox but the idea of installing nvm to install node to install npm to install &amp;gt;100 dependencies to compile a webpage is disgusting, despite how nice the page looks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
