<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>metasploit on Connor Shade</title>
    <link>https://connorshade.com/tags/metasploit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in metasploit on Connor Shade</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Connor Shade</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:29:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://connorshade.com/tags/metasploit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Making a Custom Metasploit Module</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/custom-metasploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:29:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/custom-metasploit/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to part three of service-to-shell. In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll cover the basics of exploiting DNSSearcher by using Metasploit, along with command stagers, to get a full Meterpreter session on the target. I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to cover best practices - if you have a similarly vulnerable webapp, I hope this is a useful tutorial, or something interesting to read.
Research How to get a Metasploit environment If you&amp;rsquo;re running on a machine where you want to install Metasploit (or where it&amp;rsquo;s already installed), this shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service to Shell</title>
      <link>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:46:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connorshade.com/service-to-shell/</guid>
      <description>Check out the code at github.com/cnnrshd/service-to-shell!
Summary This was a fun project. I enjoyed most of the process, the worst part was trying to troubleshoot some of the Metasploit issues I was having (especially using echo as a a cmdstager).
I made:
DNSSearcher, a vulnerable FastAPI service, then used FastAPI&amp;rsquo;s data validation to prevent command injection on an endpoint. An extremely minimal nmap-service-probe file that runs 100x faster and only detects DNSSearcher A Metasploit module that auto-checks the exploit and works with multiple payloads and stagers Artifacts So far, there are no greater contributions to the Cyber Security community as a result of this project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
